Hey friends welcome to smartphone
price
is fixed and this market is falling, we want it
but its stock is not good, 30 inch for ₹100 to ₹100,
okay, so about 200 market,
but we need stock, okay and nothing more than this, there was
some problem,
subscribe and click here
subscribe up and down, so you can
clearly see from here downwards that we want everything, but
still the irrational, this national radio is
running more, okay,
this start again, this my tablet, from this also
advisors to advice just - tanning
learning in water and talking cat just for
educational purpose of 8000, open distraction,
just make straight, absolutely okay, so
here I thought of both the people to
subscribe to this channel, okay, so now the
school is such a big parent company, subscribe, so
I want to say that general insurance, special
time, liquid, branded-branded agency
spread, how many connections of snake, from how much to
how much Maruti cars are sold,
so subscribe and make this  If I get involved then it takes a lot of
hard work, so I thought that subscribe to this channel,
subscribe to the channel, on the other
hand
when will you mute the team, then you will have to clear the school of,
okay, very much, so
whatever general insurance in this, the top
three less wars, now you have to
book circulation, you will see that till date the majority of them had done
their General Science India
Insurance National Insurance A pune, the
market plant kept losing less than the market,
this blind, that is why I have
separated both, now I
want to show you how, here 5000 and from where and
why, then okay,
you will write it here for you madam,
or
I will come and see here, it
closed yesterday at 3116,
subscribe to the recent one, 1628 30 is below this, like this,
subscribe to the market so that maximum number of
subscribers and we subscribe
and secondly, in the second video it was told that when you go to
buy a car, then you have to
subscribe,
I do not buy a car in a year, then
directly I spend 28 rupees a month on this number, so
So that is a big thing to see, if we
go into the share holding pattern, subscribe in 2018
and almost every month every month the
fog was a little warm
but there was definitely some reduction here too but in 14
years, in 2 years the most obscure ghee has been
subscribed by the public now it is school
and we are not visible, it is a
matter of thinking that why do they like it like this and
where do we find us, we have
this exam
that it is absolutely ah
yes, do it in retail where is 12.5% ​​to z
understand and efficiency quickly, quickly our
device is out how visible is it because
yours was getting it cheaply for ₹10,
so clicks on subscribe like subscribe are also
good, we will take it out from that,
what about my device that more than 3.75
times the public subscribes quickly,
you guys subscribe to this channel for stock,
subscribe to 2009 2013
operating profit has been going on operating
margin is going on okay and the same company
in the private sector, channel subscription is
good  So, let me
show you some good updates by funding
your vault, you can also use
it from the market, travel
insurance market share, okay, it is
showing 58 percent of intense pain detox,
this look stock has come out of a lot of problem
stress, that define key from
Greece top business tour operator * that our
30.7 in this was okay,
okay, free 10 percent engineering in auto insurance,
so it is quite good
fault, okay, due to this decision, it is
growing very fast, okay, so subscribe, whether you melt or not
and like it, then subscribe
and if you do not understand this, then you should see
why you should buy it, okay